{
    "subject": "resource/Red_Rock_West",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Lara_Flynn_Boyle",
    "human_readable": "Lara Flynn Boyle stars in Red Rock West.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9866464138031006,
            "question": "What role does Lara Flynn Boyle play in 'Red Rock West'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9834461808204651,
            "question": "Is Lara Flynn Boyle known for appearing in the movie 'Red Rock West'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8912619352340698,
            "question": "Besides 'Red Rock West', what other films has Lara Flynn Boyle been in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8543845415115356,
            "question": "Lara Flynn Boyle is an actress in what film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.816901683807373,
            "question": "In which film does Lara Flynn Boyle appear?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7735775113105774,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie starring Lara Flynn Boyle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7708480954170227,
            "question": "Name a movie that features Lara Flynn Boyle."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7335052490234375,
            "question": "Who stars in the film 'Red Rock West'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6751337647438049,
            "question": "What is the title of the movie featuring Lara Flynn Boyle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26325109601020813,
            "question": "What genre is the movie 'Red Rock West'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lara Flynn Boyle stars in Red Rock West.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6566_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the title of the movie featuring Lara Flynn Boyle?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6566_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who stars in the film 'Red Rock West'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6566_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a movie that features Lara Flynn Boyle.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6566_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6566_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6566_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6566_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6566_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6566_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6566_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6566_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6566_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6566_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6566_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple to be evaluated is:\n\nLara Flynn Boyle stars in Red Rock West.\n\nFrom the context information, we can see that:\n\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6566/re-ranker-msmarco/45.txt, it says \"After portraying Stacy in Penelope Spheeris's comedy Wayne's World (1992), Boyle had a lead role in John Dahl's critically acclaimed neo-noir film Red Rock West (1993)...\"\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6566/re-ranker-msmarco/54.txt, it says \"Synopsis: Michael (Nicolas Cage, Wild at Heart), a discharged marine turned drifter, ends up in Red Rock, Wyoming in search of honest work.  Wayne (J.T.  Walsh, Breakdown), a local bar owner, offers Michael the dishonest work of carrying out a hit on his wife Suzanne (Lara Flynn Boyle, The Last Seduction) after mistaking him for the actual hitman, \u201cLyle, from Dallas\u201d, that he hired to murder his spouse.\"\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6566/re-ranker-msmarco/32.txt and 45.txt, it says \"Aside from her earlier work, most people may know her as Donna Hayward from 'Twin Peaks.'  After accidentally believing she was auditioning to play the deceased character of Laura Palmer, Boyle successfully starred on the TV series from 1989 to 1991.  As a result, Boyle was a heavily sought-after actress, starring in '90s movie classics such as \"Wayne's World\" and \"Red Rock West.\"\"\n\nTherefore, the answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that Lara Flynn Boyle starred in the film \"Red Rock West\" (1993), directed by John Dahl. This information supports the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}